Guide to the Robert Trent Jones papers, ca. 1924-2003.
Jones, Robert Trent papers
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Robert Trent Jones papers, 1924-2003.
6855
Jones, Robert Trent.
804 cubic ft.
Correspondence, plans, printed materials
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Collection consists of Jones' records related to golf course design. Includes correspondence, personal material, business records, photographs, sketches, and golf course plans.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Robert Trent Jones (1906-2000) was a golf course architect. Born in Ince-in-Makerfield, England, he grew up in East Rochester, New York, where he became an avid golfer from his youth. Jones attended Cornell University, where he created his own course of study to become a professional golf course designer. During his professional career, he designed and re-designed more than 500 golf courses nationally and internationally, including 79 courses that were used for the United States Open or other national championships. Jones was a founding member and a former president of the American Society of Golf Course Architects. He won numerous awards for his designs and was the first architect inducted into the World Golf Hall of Fame in 1987.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Collection consists of Jones' records related to golf course design. Includes correspondence, personal material, business records, photographs, sketches, and golf course plans.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Jones, Robert Trent.
Subjects:
Golf.; Golf courses.; Golf courses
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Selected boxes and folders containing individuals' financial or other sensitive information are restricted. All boxes in the subseries Financial Records and Legal Affairs are restricted, including boxes 9, 14, 16, 18, 20, 26, 33, 53, 49-54, 56, 58, 60-61, 71-74, 78, 81, 116, 125-126, 135-136, 139-141, 144, 151-152, 171, 177, 197, 199, 219, 239, 249, and 301. Please refer to the collection finding aid for additional restricted folders.
RELATED MATERIALS
See also Robert Trent Jones, Jr. Memorabilia, #6856.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Biographical Information
Memorabilia
Personal Material
Personal Correspondence
Writings and Talks
Articles and Clippings
Series II. Office Records
General
Financial Records [RESTRICTED]
Legal Affairs [RESTRICTED]
Related Companies
Series III. Project Records
Project Files
Files and Technical Specifications
Correspondence for Contract Jobs
Contracts
Completed Jobs
Incomplete Jobs
Foreign Leads
Series IV. Photographs and Slides
Black and White Photographs
Color Photographs
35mm Slides
Series V. Audio Visual Materials
Films
Audio Cassettes
Series VI. Drawings and Plans
Filed Plans
Rolled Plans
United States
International
Miscellaneous
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Biographical Information
  - Memorabilia
    - Various cuff links, US Presidential seal cuff links from President Bush (Box 10)
    - Leather pouch (Box 10)
    - Gold and diamond ring from Golf Course Superintendents Association (Box 10)
    - Billfolds (Box 10)
    - Commemorative coins (Box 10)
    - Orient Express pen (Box 10)
    - Leather wallet (Box 10)
    - Gold painted golf balls (Box 10)
    - Glasses (Box 10)
    - Sharp Memo Master Alarm 600 (Box 10)
    - Rotating clock and barometer (Box 17)
    - Passport (Box 17)
    - Business cards (Box 17)
    - Framed family photograph (Box 22)
    - Keychains (Box 22)
    - Pins (Box 22)
    - Watches (Box 22)
    - Keys (Box 22)
    - Nameplates (Box 22)
    - Robert Trent Jones' drafting pens, pencils (Box 28)
    - Drafting tools (Box 28)
    - Stamps (Box 28)
    - Tape (Box 28)
    - Green and gold decanter with 6 matching glasses (Box 38)
    - Glass bell (Box 38)
    - Rectangular golf statuette (Box 38)
    - Pimpernel golf scenes (Box 38)
    - Yellow glass (Box 38)
    - Marking tacks (Box 204)
    - Desk lamp (Box 204)
    - Orange string (Box 204)
    - Pencil sharpeners (Box 204)
  - Personal Material
    - RTJ Sr. funeral expenses (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - Connelly Property (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - Eaton (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - One Main St. Co. (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - Ed Long Maintenance, Virginia Land (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - Coral Ridge Country Club, 2001 (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - Falkins, Wilson, Hunt and Co., 2002 (Box 113, Folder 7)
    - Steve Grob, 1998 (Box 113, Folder 8)
    - Gillespie and Goldman, PA (Box 113, Folder 9)
    - Shanley and Fisher, PA (Box 113, Folder 10)
    - Connelly, Dorothy (Box 113, Folder 11)
    - Lou DeReuil (Box 113, Folder 12)
    - Coral Ridge Country Club (Box 113, Folder 13)
    - Oracle Ranch planned community (Box 113, Folder 14)
    - Fuente del Berro proposal, 1992 (Box 113, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous pamphlets (Box 113, Folder 16)
    - Two framed sketches (Box 113, Folder 17)
    - Clippings and articles, 1970s-1980s (Box 120, Folder 1)
    - Articles and publications about Robert Trent Jones, 1960-1980s (Box 120, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Straile, Robert, 1953 (Box 120, Folder 3)
    - List of best golf courses, 1975-1987 (Box 120, Folder 4)
    - Suggestion for the Useful Application of Work-for-Relief Labor in New Jersey (Box 120, Folder 5)
    - Zoning ordinance, township of Bedminster, NJ (Box 120, Folder 6)
    - Appraisal Gates Ave. Contents, 1990 (Box 120, Folder 7)
    - Articles by Robert Trent Jones (Box 120, Folder 8)
    - Press Releases and Articles, 1990s (Box 120, Folder 9)
    - Mary Providence, 1960s-1980s (Box 120, Folder 10)
    - Notes (Box 120, Folder 11)
    - Badges from Congressional country club (Box 120, Folder 12)
    - Constitution and by-laws (Box 120, Folder 13)
    - Daily report and miscellaneous` (Box 120, Folder 14)
    - Personal (Box 120, Folder 15)
    - Club memberships (Box 120, Folder 16)
    - Golf tournament, 1986 (Box 120, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 120, Folder 18)
    - Personal material, address book (Box 120, Folder 19)
    - Bobby Tyre Jones scholarship (Box 120, Folder 20)
    - Cornell Foundation (Box 120, Folder 21)
    - Newbridge (Box 120, Folder 22)
    - RTJ Courses chronological list (Box 128, Folder 1)
    - Poems and fliers (Box 128, Folder 2)
    - Patents and trademarks (Box 128, Folder 3)
    - Breakwater Towers (Box 128, Folder 4)
    - Eureka Assoc., 1998 (Box 128, Folder 5)
    - Zink, Alan (Box 128, Folder 6)
    - Sun Trust (Box 128, Folder 7-8)
    - Suntrust loan payoff, 2001 (Box 128, Folder 9)
    - Midland Mortgage (Box 128, Folder 10-11)
    - Follow-ups (Box 128, Folder 12-13)
    - Goffstein, Raskas, Pomerantz, Kraus (Box 128, Folder 14)
    - RTJ Biography (Box 128, Folder 15)
    - Contents of Safes, 1988 (Box 128, Folder 16)
    - Memorabilia, the Jones Room (Box 128, Folder 17)
    - RTJ Birthday, 1997 (Box 128, Folder 18)
    - Geographical golf course listing (Box 128, Folder 19)
    - Speaking engagements, 1968-1971 (Box 214, Folder 1)
    - Metropolitan Golf Writer's Association, 1976 (Box 214, Folder 2)
    - RTJ Film "From St. Andrew's to St. Basil's" papers, 1975 (Box 214, Folder 3)
    - William Richardson Award letters and clippings, 1981 (Box 214, Folder 4)
    - Green Mountain College, Poultney VT. Honorary Degree, 1987-1988 (Box 214, Folder 5)
    - Passport material, 1987 (Box 214, Folder 6)
    - Boy's Club of New York all sports hall of fame dinner, 1986-1987 (Box 214, Folder 7)
    - PGA Hall of Fame letters, 1987 (Box 214, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 214, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: 80th birthday, 1986 (Box 214, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1981-1985 (Box 214, Folder 11-19)
    - Visas, 1970-1980s (Box 214, Folder 20)
    - Banquet of the Golden Plate Award, 1972 (Box 214, Folder 21)
    - Licensing- landscaping architects (Box 214, Folder 22-25)
    - Cornell Golf Tournament, 1975 (Box 214, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence and PR, 1976-1981 (Box 214, Folder 27-28)
    - National Institute of Social Sciences, 1976 (Box 214, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 214, Folder 30)
    - Ryder Cup Victory Dinner, 1967 (Box 231, Folder 2)
    - Dye Designs Golf Course Calendar, 1993 (Box 231, Folder 3)
  - Personal Correspondence
    - Publicity material (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Clippings from Oakmount Open, 1953 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Election clippings, 1954 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - The Dunes clippings, 1954 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Assorted Clippings, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Oak Hill open clippings, 1956 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - hole-in-one tournament clippings (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Olympic CC clippings, 1953 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - RTJ biography copies and articles (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - RTJ personal articles (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - RTJ Hall of Fame, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Clippings from Oakmount Open, 1960-1963 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Sports Illustrated articles, 1962-1965 (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Articles, clippings, magazines (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - Gold Digest: America's Greatest Public Courses (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous documents (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - Lists of planners and developments (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - Material for RTJ bio (Box 46, Folder 18)
    - Championships played on RTJ courses, 1980s (Box 46, Folder 19)
    - Africa dead leads- Egypt miscellaneous correspondence, 1971-1980 (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - Africa dead leads- Egypt Mena house plans (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - Facsimiles of RTJ drawings (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Anstalt miscellaneous plans (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - Golf Estorel St. Raphael specs, plans, 1987 (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - Stockley park plans, landscapes and contours (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - Valascure report (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - Dynacolor labelled photographs (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - Coral Ridge Food (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - Coral Ridge description, maintenance, 1962-1967 (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - Coral Ridge golf, 1965-1969 (Box 104, Folder 11)
    - Golf carts, 1961-1966 (Box 104, Folder 12)
    - American Golfers Club plans, Fort Lauderdale (Box 104, Folder 13)
    - Ashtrays, 1964 (Box 104, Folder 14)
    - Coral Ridge miscellaneous, 1974-1978 (Box 104, Folder 15)
    - Coral Ridge properties, 1961-1965 (Box 104, Folder 16)
    - Doherty, 1978 (Box 104, Folder 17)
    - Fence- Coral Ridge, 1964-1965 (Box 104, Folder 18)
    - Financial- American Golfers, 1966-1967 (Box 104, Folder 19)
    - Florida Magazines, brochures. Coral Ridge (Box 104, Folder 20)
    - Food consultants, Coral Ridge, 1967 (Box 105, Folder 21)
    - Hall, Dan, 1965-1966 (Box 105, Folder 22)
    - Harbor Beach tax association [RESTRICTED] (Box 105, Folder 23)
    - Healy, 1963-1964 (Box 105, Folder 24)
    - Healy financial reports etc. Coral Ridge, 1963 (Box 105, Folder 25)
    - History- Coral Ridge, 1965 (Box 105, Folder 26)
    - House Rules, Coral Ridge, 1962-1964 (Box 105, Folder 27)
    - Ideas and suggestions- Coral Ridge, 1963 (Box 105, Folder 28)
    - Insurance, Coral Ridge, 1961-1966 (Box 105, Folder 29)
    - Inventory, Coral Ridge, 1965 (Box 105, Folder 30)
    - Irrigation and water systems Coral Ridge, 1968-1968 (Box 105, Folder 31)
    - Kane, Vernon, 1965-1966 (Box 105, Folder 32)
    - Kirby, Ron, 1964-1965 (Box 105, Folder 33)
    - Kitchen, Existing floor plan, 1967 (Box 105, Folder 34)
    - Koopmans, C., 1964 (Box 105, Folder 35)
    - Lago Mar, 1966 (Box 105, Folder 36)
    - Landscaping, 1962 (Box 105, Folder 37)
    - Leases, duplicates, 1954 (Box 105, Folder 38)
    - Legal aspects and correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1961-1966 (Box 105, Folder 39)
    - Lighting (Box 105, Folder 40)
    - List, Mr. A, 1965-1966 (Box 105, Folder 41)
    - Mac Dougall, John, 1965 (Box 105, Folder 42)
    - Maitre D's, possible- Coral Ridge, 1964-1965 (Box 105, Folder 43)
    - Manager Applications, Coral Ridge, 1963 (Box 105, Folder 44)
    - Marina, proposed- Coral Ridge, 1965 (Box 105, Folder 45)
    - Membership List- Coral Ridge, 1962 (Box 105, Folder 46)
    - Malmstrom vs. Jones- Coral Ridge, 1965 (Box 105, Folder 47)
    - Membership, prospective, 1964-1965 (Box 105, Folder 48)
    - Membership Application form- Coral Ridge (Box 105, Folder 49)
    - Miller, Beatrice, 1966 (Box 105, Folder 50)
    - Miscellaneous, Coral Ridge, 1962-1964 (Box 105, Folder 51)
    - Morrison, Richard- Coral Ridge, 1962-1965 (Box 105, Folder 52)
    - Music- Coral Ridge, 1966 (Box 105, Folder 53)
    - IBM Country Club, 1953-1956 (Box 105, Folder 54)
    - IBM Poughkeepsie, 1944-1954 (Box 105, Folder 55)
    - IBM Poughkeepsie insurance, 1945-1946 (Box 105, Folder 56)
    - IBM Poughkeepsie, 2nd nine, 1945-1946 (Box 105, Folder 57)
    - Poughkeepsie invoices, correspondence, 1957 (Box 105, Folder 58)
    - Garden City Country Club report (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - General Electric, the Patterson Club, 1945-1946 (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - Rees Jones, Cornell, 1959 (Box 106, Folder 3)
    - Ohio State, 1936-1937 (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - National open, 1957-1958 (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - Garden City Country Club, 1935-1938 (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - Golf stories (Box 106, Folder 7)
    - King features- Famous golf holes (Box 106, Folder 8)
    - National open statistics, 1951 (Box 106, Folder 9)
    - General Electric Company-pipe, 1930 (Box 106, Folder 10)
    - General Electric Company- Bent, 1930 (Box 106, Folder 11)
    - General Electric Company- progress reports, letters, 1930 (Box 106, Folder 12)
    - General Electric Company bond, 1931 (Box 106, Folder 13)
    - Jewish Club, 1931 (Box 106, Folder 14)
    - Oakmount country club report (Box 106, Folder 15)
    - Rees and Bob high school insurance, 1956 (Box 106, Folder 16)
    - General office correspondence, 1936 (Box 106, Folder 17)
    - Ithaca Country Club, 1931 (Box 106, Folder 18)
    - Golf Game- patents and correspondence, 1930-1939 (Box 106, Folder 19)
    - Glen Mawr Golf and Country Club, estimate, 1930 (Box 106, Folder 20)
    - Contractors, 1947-1953 (Box 106, Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous, 1934-1945 (Box 106, Folder 22)
    - Ithaca Country Club, 1931-1940 (Box 106, Folder 23)
    - Cornell Golf Course, 1937-1960 (Box 106, Folder 24)
    - New York State Parks, 1931-1945 (Box 106, Folder 25)
    - Royal and Ancient membership list, 1951-1961 (Box 106, Folder 26)
    - Robinson CE, 1954-1957 (Box 106, Folder 27)
    - Publicity ideas, 1930s (Box 106, Folder 28)
    - Joe and Herb Graffis, 1934-1945 (Box 106, Folder 29)
    - Ithaca Country Club, 1952 (Box 106, Folder 30)
    - Congressional Country Club, 1953-1960 (Box 106, Folder 31)
    - Olympic Country Club, 1965-1966 (Box 106, Folder 32)
    - Olympic Country Club, 1954-1955 (Box 106, Folder 33)
    - Gardin City Country Club, 1942-1945 (Box 106, Folder 34)
    - Pine Orchard, 1946-1949 (Box 106, Folder 35)
    - Pebble Beach, 1951-1956 (Box 106, Folder 36)
    - Puerto Rico, 1955-1958 (Box 106, Folder 37)
    - Puerto Rico possible golf course sites, 1950 (Box 106, Folder 38)
    - Puerto Rico Dorado specs and bids, 1957-1961 (Box 106, Folder 39)
    - RTJ birth certificate and naturalization facsimiles (Box 121, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence A-B, 1989-1991 (Box 121, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence C-F, 1989-1991 (Box 121, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence G, 1989-1991 (Box 121, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence H-I, 1989-1991 (Box 121, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence J-L, 1989-1991 (Box 121, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence M, 1989-1991 (Box 121, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence N, 1989-1991 (Box 121, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence O-P, 1989-1991 (Box 121, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence Q-R, 1989-1991 (Box 121, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence R-S, 1989-1991 (Box 121, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence S-V, 1989-1991 (Box 121, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence W-Z, 1989-1991 (Box 121, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1989-1991 (Box 121, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous biographical books notes, 1970s-1980s (Box 121, Folder 19)
    - RTJ Licensing New Jersey, 1984 (Box 121, Folder 20)
    - RTJ Licensing Massachusetts (Box 121, Folder 21)
    - RTJ Licensing West Virginia (Box 121, Folder 22)
    - RTJ Licensing Maryland (Box 121, Folder 23)
    - RTJ Licensing North Carolina (Box 121, Folder 24)
    - RTJ Book notes (Box 121, Folder 25)
    - Joy Enval Golf Club, 1987-1989 (Box 121, Folder 26)
    - Oak Hill documents (Box 121, Folder 27)
    - Golf developments (Box 121, Folder 28)
    - Book with Sol Zatt, 1980-1983 (Box 121, Folder 29)
    - Ballybunion jackets, etc., 1988 (Box 121, Folder 30)
    - Biographical material, J Danforth film (Box 121, Folder 31)
    - Marquis Who's Who, 1972-1990 (Box 121, Folder 32)
    - Lawyers' bills [RESTRICTED], 1985-1986 (Box 121, Folder 33)
    - Lawsuits [RESTRICTED], 1989-1991 (Box 121, Folder 34)
    - Lawsuits [RESTRICTED], 1991-1992 (Box 121, Folder 35)
    - Ipswich lawsuit file [RESTRICTED], 1990-1991 (Box 121, Folder 36)
    - Birthday and Father's Day cards (Box 168, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1947-1963 (Box 168, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence-Coral Ridge--Golf and Country Club, Ft. Lauderdale (Box 168, Folder 3)
    - Golf cartoons and stories (Box 168, Folder 4)
    - Tri-county golf challenge gala--a tribute to Robert Trent Jones, 1995 (Box 168, Folder 5)
    - Ryder Cup President Dinner, Valderrama Spain programs and brochures (Box 168, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence-Honorary Degree, Green Mountain College VT, 1988 (Box 168, Folder 7)
    - Address books (Box 168, Folder 8)
    - Guest books (Box 168, Folder 9)
    - Notebook (Box 168, Folder 10)
    - Surveys, 1950s (Box 168, Folder 11)
    - Agreement, 1956-1960 (Box 168, Folder 12)
    - Old Conveyances to Syndicate, 1957 (Box 168, Folder 13)
    - Income taxes [RESTRICTED], 1960-1963 (Box 168, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1957-1961 (Box 168, Folder 15)
    - Report, notes, 1957 (Box 168, Folder 16)
    - Pine Valley Gold Course Green quantities, 1966 (Box 168, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous golf course advertisements and articles (Box 168, Folder 18)
    - Port Grimaud booklet (Box 168, Folder 19)
  - Writings and Talks
    - United States Golf Association Oral History Collection: Robert Trent Jones. Volume - Interview with Robert Trent Jones, Sr., Ft. Lauderdale, Fl. By Kendrick, Alice, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Draft of "Winged Foot Story: The Golf, the People and the Friendly Trees" by Smith, Douglas LaRue, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Great Golf Stories - Acknowledgements (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Great Golf Stories - Book Introduction (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Great Golf Stories - Jacket Biography (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Great Golf Stories - Alternative Stories for Consideration (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Great Golf Stories - Permissions (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Great Golf Stories - Contents (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Bantam, Ben Hogan (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Bisher, Furman (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Great Golf Stories - Candy, W.F. (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Campbell, Sir Guy (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Corcoran, Fred (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Great Golf Stories - Dobereiner, Peter (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Great Golf Stories - Durslag, Mel (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Great Golf Stories - Forgan, David R. (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Great Golf Stories - Grimsley, Will (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Heager, Ronald (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Hill, Dave (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Irons, D. (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Jones, Robert Trent (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Jones, Robert Trent Jr. (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Lauck, Dan (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Littler, Gene (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Longhurst, Henry (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Great Golf Stories - Martin, John Stuart (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - McDermott, Barry (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Great Golf Stories - Darwin, Bernard (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Plimpton, George (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Pope, Edwin (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Sommers, Robert (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Vardon - Golf Illustrated (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Venturi, Ken (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Wind, Herbery W. (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Wright, Ben (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Yancey, Bert (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Zatt, Sol and Company (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Articles and Clippings
    - Articles by or About Robert Trent Jones, 1951-1967 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Articles by or About Robert Trent Jones, 1951-1966 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Burdick, Dean L. "What Makes it Great", 1969-1971 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Burdick, Dean L. "What Makes it Great" - Source Material and Proofs, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Articles - Robert Trent Jones Courses, 1965-1970 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - "The Great Courses by Robert Trent Jones", 1966 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Articles, 1954-1989 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Mobil Oil Corporation Article - Pegasus, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1977 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1967-1974 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Public Relations - Articles and Clippings, 1986-1995 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Prints and Layouts of Courses (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Souvenir of Rochester (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1965 (Box 145, Folder 1)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1964 (Box 145, Folder 2)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1967 (Box 145, Folder 3)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1966 (Box 145, Folder 4)
    - Holiday Magazine, Charles Price (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - Newsweek (Box 145, Folder 6)
    - Book material, 1966 (Box 145, Folder 7)
    - Book material, 1965 (Box 145, Folder 8)
    - Magazines, 1989-2000 (Box 167, Folder 1)
    - Trail guides, maps (Box 167, Folder 2)
    - Manassas country club photographs (Box 167, Folder 3)
    - Personal and family photographs (Box 167, Folder 4)
    - Travel information (Box 167, Folder 5)
    - Golf Club booklets, packets, miscellaneous (Box 167, Folder 6)
    - Business cards (Box 167, Folder 7)
    - Golf Digest, May 1975 (Box 209, Folder 1)
    - Golf Magazine, May 1975 (Box 209, Folder 2)
    - The Golf Journal (Box 209, Folder 3)
    - Golf Magazine (Box 209, Folder 4)
    - Signature - The Magazine of the Diners Club Ltd (Box 209, Folder 5)
    - Par Golf (Box 209, Folder 6)
    - Sports Illustrated (Box 209, Folder 7)
    - Golf Digest (Box 209, Folder 8)
    - Esquire (Box 209, Folder 9)
    - Dixie Golf (Box 209, Folder 10)
    - The Book of Golf, 1970 (Box 209, Folder 11)
    - Florida Golfer (Box 209, Folder 12)
    - Life (Box 209, Folder 13)
    - Esquire (Box 209, Folder 14)
    - The National Observer - News book "The Busy Rich", 1967 (Box 209, Folder 15)
    - Look (Box 209, Folder 16)
    - Sports Illustrated Clippings, 1955-1959 (Box 209, Folder 17)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1951-1981 (Box 209, Folder 18)
    - Robert Trent Jones - Biography and Public Relations Materials (Box 209, Folder 19)
    - Clippings - Oversize, 1975 (Box 209, Folder 20)
    - Sketches of Greens (Box 209, Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous news clippings (Box 147, Folder 1-14)
- Series II. Office Records
  - General
    - Estate - Davis, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Genealogy, Ione Tefft Jones Personal, 1964-1982 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Book with Tom O'Loughlin, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Ione Scrapbook, 1927-1945 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Robert Trent Jones British Book, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Hatch Family Pictures Includes photographs correspondence with personal information, 1960-1975 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Hatch: Includes, photographs and correspondence, personal information - birth certificates. Manuscript of the Book "John Corbett, Mariner", ca. 1961-1981 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Davis, Howard Lee - Trust Fund, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Jones, Ione Davis, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Cemetery Plots, 1972-1976 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Contents of the Safes - Gates Ave. Robert Trent Jones, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Contents of the Safes - Gates Ave. Robert Trent Jones, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Excess Liability Insurance, 1976-1985 (Box 2, Folder 13)